Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs PHOTOS 023 001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs
1940s-1992
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
PHOTOS 023 001
27 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes, 2 photograph boxes, 22 record cartons, and 2 folders in oversize shared boxes and in 2 folders in flatfile cases.
District Council 65, United Automobile Workers (UAW) was organized in 1933 by a group of Jewish workers employed in dry goods warehouses on New York's Lower East Side. In 1935 it became a local of the Wholesale Dry Goods Employees Union; subsequently, it affiliated with the Distributive Trades Council of New York and the Retail Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU); it joined with the UAW in 1979. The union went out of existence in 1994, when bankruptcy forced it to close. This Collection consists of photographs spanning the late 1930s through the early 1990s, with the bulk from the 1940s, 1950s and 1980s. Besides documenting the life and times of the union itself, these images provide especially strong documentation for left and liberal causes of the 1940s-1960s, including civil rights, rank and file participation in union activities, and working class leisure and recreational activities. This images in this collection were shot by District 65's own Camera Club, which functioned as staff photographers for the union's biweekly newspaper, the Distributive Worker.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, District 65 sent a gift of their records in 1979. Photographic prints from this donation were separated into their own collection, the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs (PHOTOS 023.001). The accession numbers associated with these materials 1979.014. Six donations of photographs from the Distributive Worker made by UAW, District 65 were added to the collection between 1992 to 1994. The accession numbers associated with these donations are NPA.1992.007, NPA.1992.008, NPA.1993.001, NPA.1993.008, NPA.1994.008. 1994.016. Additional photographs have been added to this collection through a subsequent series of donations. The accession numbers associated with these materials are NPA.1999.035, NPA.2001.035, NPA.2002.026, NPA.2004.041, NPA.2004.071, and NPA.2006.093.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into four series, one of which is arranged into subseries:
Series I: Distributive Worker, 1964-1990
Subseries I:A: Internal District 65
Subseries I:B: Worksites
Subseries I:C: Historical Prints
Subseries I:D: Domestic Issues
Subseries I:E: International Issues
Subseries I:F: Negatives
Subseries I:G: Contact Sheets
Series II: Contact Prints, 1940-1964
Series III: District 65 Divisions, undated
Series IV: Unprocessed Materials, undated
Historical/Biographical Note
District Council 65, United Automobile Workers (UAW) was organized in 1933 by a group of Jewish workers employed in dry goods warehouses on New York's Lower East Side. In 1935 it became a local of the Wholesale Dry Goods Employees Union; subsequently, it affiliated with the Distributive Trades Council of New York and the Retail Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU); it joined with the UAW in 1979. The union went out of existence in 1994, when bankruptcy forced it to close.
Between 1937 and 1942, District 65 was at the center of a group of left-wing locals in New York City that organized large numbers of warehouse and retail workers; it later expanded its organizing to include white-collar workers in publishing and universities. Politically and socially active in areas beyond its own immediate concerns, District 65 was an early participant in the civil rights movement, as well as one of the first labor unions to publicly oppose the war in Vietnam. It took a progressive stance within its own organization also, with rank and file members playing an active role in their union.
Related Archival Materials
United Automobile, Aircraft, and Vehicle Workers of America, District 65 Records (WAG 006)
United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Oral History Collection (OH 019)
United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Printed Ephemera Collection (PE 016)
United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Negatives and Interpositives (PHOTOS 023)
Roger Keeran Photographs (PHOTOS 187)
Ed Roth Photographs Collection (PHOTOS 160)
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of approximately 34,000 primarily black and white photographs spanning the late 1930s through the early 1990s, with the bulk from the 1940s, 1950s and 1980s. Besides documenting the life and times of the union itself, these images provide especially strong documentation for left and liberal causes of the 1940s-1960s, including civil rights, rank and file participation in union activities, and working class leisure and recreational activities. What particularly distinguishes these photographs from most collections of labor union images—which are largely limited to formal shots of the leadership and its activities—is that the Collection documents the everyday organizational life of District 65 and that of its diverse membership (including men and women of Jewish, African-American, Irish and Hispanic descent), as well as its leaders. Still more unusual, and probably unique among photographs shot for labor unions, the images in Series I – Subseries C (Historical Prints), Series II (Contact Prints), as well as some in Series III, were shot by District 65's own Camera Club, which functioned as staff photographers for the union's biweekly newspaper (known variously as New Voices, Union Voice, RWDSU Record, and The 65er). Because these volunteer photographers were themselves members of District 65, shooting from the inside of the organization, they were able to capture more relaxed, intimate views of fellow members than the images shot by the commercial contract photographers usually engaged by other unions.
In the process of recording the organizational occupational, recreational, and political activities, and (occasionally) the home lives of its members and leaders, the Camera Club's images also captured a wealth of valuable historical and social information. Warehouses, offices, factories; the storefronts, facades, and interiors of dozens of department stores (the union's members worked in dozens of now-vanished department stores that were then ubiquitous in cities large and small throughout of the U.S.), marquees and interiors of hotels, auditoria, nightclubs, and other public spaces; young working people at parties and dances and engaged in amateur team sports, retired workers, workers' homes and workplaces, streetscapes of New York City, and unguarded social interactions of working people are only some of the examples of the types of visual data that can be discerned from these images. In many cases the "unintentional" documentation that is contained in these images may as valuable as the documentation they hold of the events they were meant to record. The remainder of the images in the collection, more typically, were shot by various commercial photographers.
The first series of this collection is comprised of the photo morgue of The Distributive Worker (the union's newspaper from 1969-1994), the second series includes contact prints of some of the negatives contained in the collection United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Negatives (PHOTOS 023), and the third series includes photographs documenting the union's different divisions, which were organized by industry.
Labor union meetings |z New York (State) |z New York |v Pictorial works.; Strikes and lockouts |x Retail trade |z New York (State) |z New York.; Strikes and lockouts |z New York (State) |z New York |v Pictorial works.; Photographs.; Work environment |z New York (State) |z New York |v Pictorial works.; Labor unions -- Officials and employees.; Robinson, Cleveland L. (Cleveland Lowellyn), 1914-1995; Distributive Workers of America. District 65.; Brown, Frank; American Federation of Labor. Wholesale Dry Good Employees Union. Local 19932 (New York, N.Y.).; Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union. Local 3 (New York, N.Y.).; Livingston, David; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. District 65.; Distributive, Processing, and Office Workers of America. District 65.
- Series I: Distributive Worker, 1964-1990
  - Subseries I:A Internal District 65
    - Box 10, undated
      Scope and Content Note
      Arts Activities, Building, Credit Union, Education Programs (Stewards Training, Hofstra and Rutgers)
    - Box 11, undated
      Education Programs, Demonstrations and Rallies, Employment and Unemployment, Executive Council Meetings, Ethnic Affairs (Black Affairs).
    - Box 12, 1984-1989
      Ethnic Affairs (Black, Hispanic, Italian, Irish and Jewish Affairs), Finance, General Council Meetings
    - Box 13, undated
      General Council Meetings, Staff and Local Officer Portraits, Labor Leader and Celebrity Portraits, Group Portraits.
    - Oversize Materials, 1957 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 14)
      Meetings and conventions.
    - Box 14, undated
      Staff and Local Officer Portraits, Labor Leader and Celebrity Portraits, Group Portraits.
    - Box 15, undated
      Labor Leader and Celebrity Portraits, Group Portraits, District 65 Shops.
    - Box 16, undated
      District 65 Shops.
    - Box 32, undated
      District 65 shops.
    - Box 17, 1980s
      District 65 Shops, Divisions (Apparel, Buttons, Chemical and Paint, Colleges).
    - Box 18, 1980s
      Divisions (Colleges, Direct Mail, Display).
    - Box 19, undated
      Divisions (Legal, Shoes, Textiles, Toys and Gift, Wholesale), Defunct Locals.
    - Box 20, undated
      Defunct Locals, UAW and District 65 Affiliation and Locals, Meetings and Conventions.
    - Box 21, undated
      Meetings and Conventions.
    - Oversize Materials, 1954 (Box OS006, Folder 1, Flat-file 7, Drawer 15)
    - Box 22, undated
      Members' Families, Members' Assistance Plans, Organizing, Publicity, Rank and File, Community Participation, Retirees.
    - Box 23, 1978-1990
      Retirees, Security Plan (Health, Doctors, Medical Plans).
    - Box 24, undated
      Security Plan (Medical Plans, Optical, Pharmacy), Social and Recreation Events, Strikes and Lockouts.
    - Box 25, undated
      Union Elections, Youth, Health and Safety, Disaster Relief, Travel.
  - Subseries I:B Worksites
    - Box 25, undated
      Work Sites.
  - Subseries I:C Historical Prints
    - Box 25, undated
      Historical Prints.
    - Box 26, undated
      Historical prints.
  - Subseries I:D Domestic Issues
    - Box 26, 1964-1991
      Anti-Nuclear, Peace, Vietnam, Civil Rights and Anti-Discrimination.
    - Box 27, 1984-1991
      Civil Rights and Anti-Discrimination, Employment, Energy, Housing, Labor, Labor Day.
    - Box 28, 1984-1991
      Labor Day, Union Solidarity, New York City and New York State Politics, National Politics, Women's Issues, Budget, Healthcare, Environment, Media, Transportation, Immigration.
  - Subseries I:E International Issues
    - Box 28, undated
      General International Issues, South Africa, Gulf War, Latin America, Caribbean, Europe.
    - Box 29, undated
      South Africa, Israel.
  - Subseries I:F Negatives
    - Box 29, undated
      Negatives with Matching Contact Sheets.
  - Subseries I:G Contact Sheets
    - Box 30, 1960s; 1982-1990
      Contact Sheets (No matching Negatives)
- Series II: Contact Prints, 1940-1964
  - Naradowitz, Sol - in uniform, Jan 24, 1942; 00439 (Box 8)
  - Kelman, Joe - Going to the Army, Jan 24, 1942; 00441 (Box 8)
  - Women Conference Committee, Jan 1942; 00443 (Box 8)
  - A night at Local 65 - Feature Story, Jan 1942; 00447 (Box 8)
  - NYA Student (union member), Jan 1942; 00448 (Box 8)
  - Crown Novelty Party, Jan 28, 1942; 00449 (Box 8)
  - Kahn, Herb - Going to the Army, Jan 1942; 00451 (Box 8)
  - Lerners Arbitration, Jan 1942; 00452 (Box 8)
  - First Aid Class, Feb 5, 1942; 00467 (Box 8)
  - CIO Ambulance Auxiliary Women, Feb 1942; 00469 (Box 8)
  - Harlem Social, Feb 13, 1942; 00476 (Box 8)
  - Harlem Social - musicians, Feb 13, 1942; 00476 (Box 8)
  - Dorset Foods" [group portrait of women] (See also negative #00987.), undated; 00481 (Box 8)
  - Dorset Foods Strike" [Three-shot of women, two of whom display bandaged hands--acquired in a strike-related scuffle?] (See also negative #00987.), undated; 00481 (Box 8)
  - Miles Arbitration, Feb 1942; 00483 (Box 8)
  - Ninth Annual, Feb 28, 1942; 00490 (Box 8)
  - Sat. Nite Jamboree, Mar 1942; 00503 (Box 8)
  - Publix Metal - woman working heavy machinery, Mar 1942; 00508 (Box 8)
  - Bennett Box Shop Meeting (This is a modern copy neg., produced for the Feb. 1989 Pictures of our lives exhibit 4x5 print exists, undated; 00539 (Box 8)
  - U-5 Membership Meeting, Apr 29, 1942; 00544 (Box 8)
  - Book Booth - 469 Seventh Ave., Apr 30, 1942; 00545 (Box 8)
  - Miles Shoe - 05-01-42, Apr 30, 1942; 00546 (Box 8)
  - May Day, Apr 12, 1942; 00548 (Box 8)
  - Dixie Mail Order, May 1, 1942; 00549 (Box 8)
  - May Day meeting, May 1, 1942; 00550 (Box 8)
  - Harlem Game Night, May 1, 1942; 00552 (Box 8)
  - Harlem Game Night, 1942; 00552 (Box 8)
  - Softball- Randall's Island, undated; 00553 (Box 8)
  - Brownsville Social (May Day), May 2, 1942; 00554 (Box 8)
  - Libassi - Interview (May Day), May 6, 1942; 00555 (Box 8)
  - Blood donation - Red Cross, May 6, 1942; 00557 (Box 8)
  - White, Lillian, May 15, 1942; 00560 (Box 8)
  - Head - Midshipman, May 16, 1942; 00561 (Box 8)
  - Beskin, Lon - Draftee, May 1942; 00565 (Box 8)
  - Finance Department - Inventory, May 1942; 00566 (Box 8)
  - Western Front Petitions - D-5, May 1942; 00568 (Box 8)
  - Womens' War Committee, AFL, CIO, May 21, 1942; 00569 (Box 8)
  - Open Air Rally D-1, May 22, 1942; 00570 (Box 8)
  - Boat Ride 1942, May 24, 1942; 00572 (Box 8)
  - Breakstones, May 28, 1942; 00574 (Box 8)
  - Meigide, Doug - Wedding, May 29, 1942; 00575 (Box 8)
  - Mack, Gerrie and Husband, May 29, 1942; 00576 (Box 8)
  - Construction - 13 Astor Place, Jun 3, 1942; 00578 (Box 8)
  - Baseball Game - Big 6, Jun 6, 1942; 00580 (Box 8)
  - Weinstock, Louis and Osman, Arthur -construction -13 Astor Place, Jun 9, 1942; 00582 (Box 8)
  - Coast Guard, undated; 00585 (Box 8)
  - Hiring Hall, undated; 00586 (Box 8)
  - Hiring Hall, undated; 00586 (Box 8)
  - Western Front Rally - D-2, Jun 12, 1942; 00591 (Box 8)
  - Dubjack, Edna, Jun 15, 1942; 00596 (Box 8)
  - Harlem Social, Jun 26, 1942; 00609 (Box 8)
  - Band Rehearsal, Jul 15, 1942; 00622 (Box 8)
  - Sol Molofsky - Farewell Party, Jul 18, 1942; 00625 (Box 8)
  - Arthur Beir Check Presentation, Jul 22, 1942; 00628 (Box 8)
  - Woolworth meeting, undated; 00789 (Box 8)
  - New Voices Dist. - Woolworth, undated; 00797 (Box 8)
  - B. Div. Cafe Social, undated; 00835 (Box 8)
  - Kernes Parents, undated; 00845 (Box 8)
  - Hiring Hall (x women) (x blacks), undated; 00853 (Box 8)
  - Lerners Red Cross Drive (x women), undated; 00855 (Box 8)
  - Dance (x blacks), undated; 00856 (Box 8)
  - 10th Annual Dance - (x blacks) (x women), undated; 00857 (Box 8)
  - Conferance on Distribution Industry during the war [Osman?], undated; 00914 (Box 8)
  - Bush, Harry - in shoe market, undated; 00925 (Box 8)
  - Bush, Harry Farewell Party, undated; 00926 (Box 8)
  - Hill, George Leaving for Army ["Portrait" feature] ["Capsule Biography" feature] -, undated; 00928 (Box 8)
  - Kaplan, Harry Lt. ["Portrait" feature] ["Capsule Biography" feature]., undated; 00937 (Box 8)
  - Capt. Mulzac visiting 65, undated; 00938 (Box 8)
  - Downing, John ["Portrait" feature] ["Capsule Biography" feature]., undated; 00945 (Box 8)
  - Manheim, Phil - ["Portrait" feature], undated; 00946 (Box 8)
  - Dordick, Dave ["Portrait" feature], undated; 00957 (Box 8)
  - Sherbell, Kenny and Arthur Osman, undated; 00958 (Box 8)
  - Shoenfeld Shop - shipping spices, undated; 01028 (Box 8)
  - East Side Community Story, undated; 01040 (Box 8)
  - F. W. Woolwoth Meeting, undated; 01160 (Box 8)
  - D-2 presents Ambulance, Mar 1, 1944; 01172 (Box 8)
  - Opt. Res. Army - Navy E Awards, undated; 01181 (Box 8)
  - Apparel and Shoe Social, undated; 01284 (Box 8)
  - Diamond, Max - Scrap Book ["Portrait" feature], undated; 01409 (Box 8)
  - Frikushima, Ray, Dec 29, 1945; 01812 (Box 8)
  - 2nd Biennial Convention - Local 65, undated; 02078 (Box 8)
  - Pinrose Display signs contract, undated; 02093 (Box 8)
  - Brownsville Community Beach party [Rockaway Beach], undated; 02115 (Box 8)
  - Picket Woolworth stores, undated; 02124 (Box 8)
  - Macy Demonstration, undated; 02128 (Box 8)
  - OPA Rally in G5 market, undated; 02133 (Box 8)
  - S and B Mass Demonstration, undated; 02143 (Box 8)
  - Woolworth at Conciliation, undated; 02144 (Box 8)
  - Kness gets leaflets from Woolworth, undated; 02147 (Box 8)
  - Janas, Vic - Woolworth Interview ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02149 (Box 8)
  - Lasis, Albert - 5 year Woolworth worker ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02149 (Box 8)
  - Tomaino, Horation - #24; #23 Phil Janas, #22 Edwin Newcomer ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02149 (Box 8)
  - Grismer, Eddie - 6 year Woolworth worker ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02149 (Box 8)
  - Blake, John - 17 year Woolworth worker] "Portrait" feature], undated; 02149 (Box 8)
  - Janas, Phil - Woolworth interview] ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02149 (Box 8)
  - Farr, Merle - 10 year Woolworth worker] ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02149 (Box 8)
  - Leaflet distribution at Penny, undated; 02150 (Box 8)
  - Schwartz, A. and Son, undated; 02157 (Box 8)
  - Schranz and Bieber strike, undated; 02159 (Box 8)
  - 65 Pickets Swifts against high prices, undated; 02160 (Box 8)
  - D.G. and F.W. Rally for a free Palestine, undated; 02165 (Box 8)
  - Textile Workers vote strike, undated; 02166 (Box 8)
  - S and B office girls picketing, undated; 02167 (Box 8)
  - Textile Mobilizes at 469 - 7th, undated; 02168 (Box 8)
  - Kornhaber Triplets, 6 months old, undated; 02169 (Box 8)
  - Kornhaber Triplets, 6 months old, undated; 02169 (Box 8)
  - Berman, B. and Brewery Union Heads] ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02170 (Box 8)
  - S and B S. Claus Demonstration, undated; 02171 (Box 8)
  - Livingston Addresses Textile strikers, undated; 02176 (Box 8)
  - Livingston: Press interviews Livingston, undated; 02177 (Box 8)
  - A.B.C. workers go to Providence, undated; 02186 (Box 8)
  - TMHA Band, undated; 02190 (Box 8)
  - Sherbell, Kenny ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02192 (Box 8)
  - Sherbell, Kenny ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02192 (Box 8)
  - Boone, Larkin and Irvin Rubin, Footwear Div.] ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 02195 (Box 8)
  - Frachtman, Tillie, Hill Lalin, Food and Drug Div.] ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 02195 (Box 8)
  - Kornbluth, Shirley, I.H. Cohen and Sons, Dry Goods Div.] ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 02195 (Box 8)
  - Kornreich, Dave ["Inquiring Photographer" feature] [Would you vote to re-elect Truman? Why? UV 9/28/46 A. Silverstein, photographer, D. Cohn, interviewer], undated; 02195 (Box 8)
  - Prosniewski, Victor ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 02195 (Box 8)
  - Ankist, Thomas ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 02195 (Box 8)
  - Unidentified ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 02195 (Box 8)
  - Levy, Harry ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 02195 (Box 8)
  - Vessiechio, Saverio S. ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 02195 (Box 8)
  - 1946-47 Bowling Opener, undated; 02196 (Box 8)
  - Textile Strike Meeting, undated; 02205 (Box 8)
  - Norsid Ad Contract, Oct 1, 1946; 02206 (Box 8)
  - Dry Goods Strike, Oct 4, 1946; 02218 (Box 8)
  - Dry Goods strikers picket Bosses homes, Oct 9, 1946; 02222 (Box 8)
  - TMHA Children's class, undated; 02223 (Box 8)
  - Nemco Picket, undated; 02226 (Box 8)
  - Geller, Dave [of H. Coken and Son ] ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02227 (Box 8)
  - Geller, Dave, Oct 15, 1946; 02227 (Box 8)
  - Tamburo, Mick [of J. Rosenholz, Stein and Fishman] ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02228 (Box 8)
  - Tamburo, Nick, Oct 15, 1946; 02228 (Box 8)
  - Nymco Strike, undated; 02230 (Box 8)
  - J.C. Penny Demonstration, undated; 02254 (Box 8)
  - Interview with Scheiffelin strikers, undated; 02261 (Box 8)
  - Inquiring Photographer, undated; 02358 (Box 8)
  - Kaesur, Lillian ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02390 (Box 8)
  - Boat Ride, undated; 02468 (Box 8)
  - Carole Stupell Demonstration, undated; 02480 (Box 8)
  - Kiddie Kontest Awards and Show [probably 06/47], undated; 02481 (Box 8)
  - Corrug. Association Negotiation, undated; 02482 (Box 8)
  - Wiltkowski (Local 144), undated; 02499 (Box 8)
  - Jacques, Hector ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02579 (Box 8)
  - Joyce Klein [portait feature], undated; 02628 (Box 8)
  - Kiddie Show, undated; 02638 (Box 8)
  - Stillman, Rose ["Inquiring Photographer" feature] [How does your living standard this year compare with last year's? UV 12/7/47 A. SIlverstein, photographer, D. Shaw. intvw], undated; 02658 (Box 8)
  - Elliot, James [What would you like for Christmas? UV 12/21/47 A. SIlverstein, photographer, D. Shaw, interviewer] ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 02661 (Box 8)
  - Martin, Carol, undated; 02667 (Box 8)
  - Williams, Eileen of Local 3 ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02675 (Box 8)
  - Xmas Parties at D.S.U. + 65, undated; 02678 (Box 8)
  - Tomaselli at Chesters Zunbarg, undated; 02683 (Box 8)
  - Lerner Negotiations, undated; 02691 (Box 8)
  - Laurie, Mary - Local 2 ["Portrait" feature], undated; 02692 (Box 8)
  - Dry Goods Association Dinner, undated; 02743 (Box 8)
  - U.V. Forum on Henry Wallace, undated; 02752 (Box 8)
  - Palestine protest Demonst. in rain, undated; 02757 (Box 8)
  - May Day Parade, undated; 02815 (Box 8)
  - Krolich, Ruth, undated; 02862 (Box 8)
  - 1948 Boat Ride, undated; 02865 (Box 8)
  - Krolick, Ruth at resort], undated; 02898 (Box 9)
  - Zunbarg, undated; 02898 (Box 9)
  - 1948-9 Bowling season opens, undated; 02974 (Box 9)
  - Jewish Labor Council, 1948, undated; 03068 (Box 9)
  - Unidentified ["Inquiring Photographer" feature], undated; 03101 (Box 9)
  - Unemployed sign cards for unemployment ins., undated; 03140 (Box 9)
  - Kiddie Carnival,Dunham dancers, undated; 03196 (Box 9)
  - DTC meeting, undated; 03226 (Box 9)
  - May Day Parade, undated; 03235 (Box 9)
  - Ruggiero, Lou [with family], undated; 03236 (Box 9)
  - Washington Delegation, undated; 03267 (Box 9)
  - Beauty Contest Winner and Week vacation at Chester [Chester's Zumbarg], undated; 03299 (Box 9)
  - Pickover, Irving ["Portrait" feature, we have a print] - copy, undated; 03318 (Box 9)
  - Jewish Labor Bazaar Committee (Wohl), undated; 03400 (Box 9)
  - Namm Security Plan, Vito Gentile and Family, undated; 03472.1 (Box 9)
  - Sweepstakes Winner Harry Dyckoff, undated; 03600 (Box 9)
  - Brown, Al Phila. Leader with Osman and Livingston, undated; 03701 (Box 9)
  - Tom Mooney Hall, 8th Floor Damage [from fire], undated; 03725 (Box 9)
  - Inquiring Photgrapher feature], undated; 03866 (Box 9)
  - Dennett Shop Lockout, undated; 03900 (Box 9)
  - Department Stores - Exteriors Macy's, Bloomingdale's, Stern,s, Saks, Namms, Loesers, Hearns, undated; 03947 (Box 9)
  - Memphis Loc Shop Mtg, undated; 04103 (Box 9)
  - Dade City - Leaders, undated; 04232 (Box 9)
  - Buckeye Worker, Memphis Tenn., undated; 04234 (Box 9)
  - Consumer Service, undated; 04300 (Box 9)
  - Phila Meeting, Organizers, undated; 04435 (Box 9)
  - Philly organizing mobilization, undated; 04444 (Box 9)
  - Trenton Bowlers, undated; 04512 (Box 9)
  - Sims (Charlotte N.C.) [Every member an organizer], undated; 04525 (Box 9)